# Joanna Colson

An inquisitive, industrious and dedicated full-stack web developer with extensive business and information technology experience. An enthusiastic team member, I learn quickly and independently, using a logical, analytical approach to produce consistent, reliable results. I thrive where talent, teamwork and life balance are valued.

Seattle, WA 98121 (425) 533-1302

joannacolson@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/joannacolson

GitHub:

github.com/joannacolson

# **PROJECTS**

**Monument Landing Page** — Responsive Front-End Layout Studying in General Assembly's Web Development Intensive program, learning three full-stack methodologies in their 12-week program.

**Map Book Viewer** — *Address Book with Map & Street Views* Studying in General Assembly's Web Development Intensive program, learning three full-stack methodologies in their 12-week program.

## **EXPERIENCE**

**General Assembly,** Seattle, WA — Web Development Student

March 2017 - Present

Studying in General Assembly's Web Development Intensive program, learning three full-stack methodologies in their 12-week program.

**Amazon,** Kent, WA — Seasonal Process Assistant
April 2016 - Present

**U.S. Postal Service,** Seattle, WA — *City Carrier Assistant*July 2015 - April 2016

**CG Tech Services,** Seattle, WA — Office Manager

September 2014 - April 2015

Managed a small tech design firm's office operations, working with the technical, administrative and accounting staff to run the office.

**Falco Sult & Co.,** Redmond, WA — *Technology Consultant*April 2007 - February 2010

Led the IT Business Consulting practice. Analysed requirements, designed and implemented technology solutions for client businesses.

### **EDUCATION**

**Bellevue College,** Bellevue, WA — Associate of Arts

AA in Network Services & Computing Systems, graduated with High Distinction.

**University of Washington, Seattle, WA** — Bachelor of Arts

BA in Business Administration, Quantitative Methods focus, Summa Cum Laude.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and JQuery.

Git and GitHub.

Flexbox and Bootstrap.

JSON, AJAX and APIs.

SQL, PostgreSQL, Postico, Node.js, Express, ORM, Sequelize.

Auth and OAuth.

Mocha, Chai and Supertest.

Ruby on Rails, AngularJS, ReactJS, Ruby.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

**Certificate of Achievement -** Cisco Support Technician

**Certificate of Achievement -**Microsoft Network Support

Microsoft Certified Desktop Support Technician (MCDST)

Microsoft Certified Systems Administrator (MCSA)

Microsoft Certified Systems Engineer (MCSE)

#### **PERSONAL INTERESTS**

Avid student of nutritional science, applied to the global diabetes & obesity epidemics.